Guide to the Charles Baptie photograph collection, 1917-1995
George Mason University Libraries
- Series 1: Buildings: Interiors and Exteriors, 1947-1975
  - Buildings, 1959-1975 (Box 39)
    Building interiors and exteriors for Woodlawn, Oswaldo Altamirano - Ecuador, and Washington, D.C., monuments. (negatives)
  - Buildings, 1960s (Box 40)
    Interior and exterior building views from malaria testing and prevention series and toy and poster makers.
  - Buildings, 1952-1967 (Box 41)
    Interior and exterior building views of St. John's Church, Hot Shoppes, Billy Martin's Carriage house, Rive Gauche interior, S and W Cafeteria, Paul Young's Restaurant Safari Lounge, Hotel Continental, Roosevelt Hotel, Statler hotel, Windsor Park hotel, Lord and Taylor, Gas Equipment Center, Texaco Service Station, White House, Fort Lincoln, and ILS Institute. (with negatives)
  - Buildings, 1953-1968 (Box 42)
    Building exteriors and interiors of Washington, D.C., monuments, Griffith Stadium, Georgetown, Anderson house, Arts Club, Cosmos Club, Bacon house, Belgium embassy, Belmont, Brazilian embassy, John Co and house, Decatur house, Firenze house, Kreeger house, Meridian house, Mexican embassy, Morris house, Octagon house, Sen. Pell house, Prospect house, Woodrow Wilson house, Woodlawn, and ballet of Monte Carlo.
  - Buildings, 1960s (Box 43)
    Building exteriors of a briefing room, Affair club, Texaco, Red Cross Canteen, Officers Club reception, Air Traffic Command, Hamamitt, Carol Steve, and Mr. Hodge [Rio].
  - Buildings, 1960s (Box 44)
    Building exteriors and interiors of vacation or foreign travel; Ecuador; Guatemala; malaria prevention; Mt. Vernon; and McIlvaine Building. (with negatives)
  - Buildings, 1947-1952 (Box 45)
    Images of building interiors and exteriors of Texaco (on Duke St.), St. Agnes School, Embassy Dairy, Pepsi Cola Plant, Cathedral, Virginia Theatre series, Christ Church anniversary, Gadsby Tavern, Lee Mansion, and [Maryland] Co. old plant. (negatives)
  - Buildings, 1960s-1970s (Box 46)
    Interior and exterior images of Waynewood, Great House, and Dumbarton. (negatives)
  - Buildings, 1948-1996 (Box 47)
    Building exterior and interior images of Town and Country bank, George Mason College, Short post club, John Torches group, Tahj Mahal, Statler, and Dickerson. (negatives)
  - Buildings, 1970s (Box 48)
    Negatives of a house interior.
  - Buildings, 1960s (Box 49)
    Interior and exterior views of Alexandria Hospital, Hotels and restaurants,and Mrs. Hunt's old house. (negatives)
  - Buildings, 1960s (Box 50)
    Building interior and exterior views relating to malaria prevention and testing campaign.
  - Buildings, 1960s (Box 51)
    White house interior images; Embassy of Iran interior shots, and Washington, D.C., monuments inside and out.
  - Buildings, 1960s (Box 52)
    Snail house exterior, Willist and Van Milin house exterior, Nolah Bunaldy house exterior, All Sports Awards house exterior, Mike Koen house exterior,Justin Bacon house exterior, Holiday Inn, Sona's Motel interior, APEX liquor store exterior, Naylors restaurant interior, and Ralerge Hotel interior. (negatives)
  - Buildings, 1940s-1950s (Box 53)
    Mayer and Co. Furniture store interior, Exxon station exterior, Washington, D.C., monuments, White House exterior, Shirlington garage, Gadsby Tavern interior, St. Clements Church exterior, Lee Mansion, and Northern Virginia Now and Then showcasing building exteriors.
  - Buildings, 1960s-1970s (Box 56)
    Waynewood exterior and interior, Great House exterior, Brent House exterior, Decatur house exterior, and Anderson house interior. (negatives)
  - Buildings, 1960s (Box 57)
    Images of a famous house in Georgetown (exterior), Dumbarton House interior, and inside the Sully Plantation. (with negatives)
  - Buildings, 1940s, 1966, 1960s (Box 58)
    Images of famous houses in the Washington, D.C., area, Gunston Hall, Washington, D.C., Monuments, arial photographs of buildings.
  - Buildings, 1950s-1960s (Box 59)
    Interior and exterior images of the White House, the Turkish Embassy, Dunbarton, Mexican embassy, Brazilian embassy, Waynewood, Elen May, Peruvian Embassy, and Mrs. Post House. (negatives)
  - The Starling Nuisance: He's Driving Everybody Crazy, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    Building interior in the series The Starling Nuisance: It's Driving me crazy.
  - Buildings, 1975 (Box 62)
    Oversized images of the exterior of the NASA building, church exteriors, Gunston Hall, and a silo.
  - Embassies, 1950s-1960s (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Interior and exterior views of several embassies, including Belgian Embassy, French Embassy, Irish Embassy, Spanish Embassy, and Turkish Embassy.
  - Portfolio, 1950s-1960s (Box 63, Folder 7)
    Images of interior and exterior of buildings, including the White House in a larger format print.
  - Buildings, 1950s-1960s (Box 63, Folder 8)
    Interior and exterior views of Belmont Mansion, Christ Church, Post House, Dumbarton Oaks, Hillwood House, Kreegar House, Library of Congress, Prospect House, Supreme Court Building, White House, and Woodlawn.
  - Buildings, 1970s (Box 64)
    Interior and exterior views of Dumbarton Oaks, Spanish Embassy, Firenze House, Cosmos Club, Turkish Embassy, Worthington House, EverMay Sunroom, Irish Embassy, Brazilian Embassy, The Lindens, Kreegar House, Tudor Place, Mexican Embassy, Belgian Embassy, Hillwood, Eastern Star Temple, French Embassy, and Anderson House.
  - Buildings, 1980s (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Oversized pictures and negatives of building interiors and exteriors.
  - Buildings, 1950s-1960s (Box 66, Folder 6)
    Oversized pictures and negatives of building interiors and exteriors including the Spanish Embassy, Turkish Embassy.
  - Houses, Yards, and Miscellaneous Buildings, 1950s-1960s (Box 68, Folder 5)
    Oversized images of Irish Embassy, Eisenhower Executive Building, Post House, Dumbarton Oaks, Anderson House.
  - Restaurant, Store, and Theatre interiors, 1940s (Box 68, Folder 6)
    Oversized images of restaurants, stores and theater interiors.
  - Churches, 1970s-1980s (Box 69, Folder 3)
    Images of churches in larger print formats.
  - Home Interiors, 1950s (Box 69, Folder 6)
    Various home interiors including the Brazilian Embassy, the Post House, Turkish Embassy, Tudor Place, in larger print formats.
  - Miscellaneous, 1950s (Box 69, Folder 7)
    Pictures and negatives of buildings in larger print formats.
- Series 2: Embassies, 1950s-1970s
  This series contains photographic prints, negatives and slides that show various embassies. Some of these photographs appear in other series based on the image. The embassies shown include the Belgian, Brazilian, French, Irish, Mexican, Peruvian, Spanish, and Turkish embassies.
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Embassies and Houses, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Embassies, 1950s-1960s (Box 28)
    Views of Spanish Embassy.
  - Embassies, 1950s-1960s (Box 32)
    Views of Mexican Embassy, Irish Embassy (negatives)
  - Embassies, 1968 (Box 42)
    Views of the Belgian, Brazilian, and Mexican embassies. (negatives)
  - Embassies, 1960s (Box 51)
    Views of the Embassy of Iran. (negatives)
  - Embassies, 1950s-1960s (Box 59)
    Views of the Turkish, Mexican, Brazilian, and Peruvian embassies. (negatives)
  - Embassies, 1950s-1960s (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Large format prints of the Belgian, French, Irish, Spanish, and Turkish embassies.
  - Embassies, 1970s (Box 64)
    Large format prints of the Spanish Embassy ballroom and patio; the Turkish Embassy entrance; the Irish Embassy garden; the Brazilian Embassy ballroom and dining room; the Mexican Embassy music room, solarium, and entrance hallway; the Belgian Embassy library and salon; and the French Embassy drawing room and exteriors.
  - Embassies, 1950s-1960s (Box 66, Folder 6)
    Oversized pictures and negatives of building interiors and exteriors including the Spanish Embassy, Turkish Embassy
  - Embassies, 1950s-1960s (Box 68, Folder 5)
    Oversize images of the Irish Embassy.
  - Embassies, 1950s (Box 69, Folder 6)
    Various home interiors including the Brazilian Embassy and Turkish Embassy in larger print formats.
- Series 3: Art, 1947-1975
  This series contains photographic prints, negatives and slides that show artwork. Some of these photographs appear in other series based on the image. The artwork includes that for a baseball book, an Encyclopedia of American History, a History of the Civil War, a Northern Virginia guidebook, as well as paintings, sculptures, dolls, trophies, and architecture.
  - Baseball Book, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
    Photographs and diagrams to illustrate a book about baseball. (with negatives)
  - Encyclopedia of American History, undated (Box 3, Folder 4-21)
    Images and artwork used to illustrate the encyclopedia.
  - History of the Civil War, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Artwork and images to illustrate a publication on the Civil War.
  - Northern Virginia Guide Books Pictures, 1960s (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Images and artwork from around Northern Virginia for a guide book. (with negatives)
  - Glass, undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Miscellaneous art.
  - Miscellaneous, 1953-1957 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - All Sports, 1970s (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Sports trophies and plaques. (negatives)
  - National Memorial Park, 1955-1961 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Artwork from the National Memorial Park.
  - Pictures of Artwork, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
    Photographs of various works of art.
  - Harry Clarkson Home, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    Photographs of artwork within Harry Clarkson's home.
  - Photos of Artwork, 1966 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    Photographs of artwork.
  - Marine General portrait, 1950s (Box 22, Folder 18)
    Photographs of portraits of Marine generals.
  - Art, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
    Drawings of houses including Pohick Church, Calvin Run Mill, Mount Vernon, and Gunston Hall.
  - Artwork, undated (Box 22, Folder 20)
    Photographs of artwork from Christ Church.
  - Artwork, undated (Box 22, Folder 21)
    Photographs of paintings.
  - Artwork, 1950s-1960s (Box 25)
    Various artwork within Little Theatre, DAR, Blair House, Statler Hotel, Sand Meridian, Shrine of Immaculate Conception, Harvey Rest, Holiday Inn, Kenmore's house, or a Uranium ore sample. (with negatives)
  - Artwork, 1950s-1960s (Box 27)
    Artwork within ideas for bicentennial celebration, Gunston Hall, Smithsonian artifacts, and Washington, D.C., monuments. (with negatives)
  - Artwork, 1950s (Box 35)
    Religious artwork, Mrs. Meticals artwork, and Mrs. Mitiary artwork. (negatives)
  - Artwork, 1960s-1970s (Box 36)
    Images of ideas for bicentenial celebration, dolls, art, and furniture.
  - Artwork, 1960s (Box 38)
    Artwork from within the Windsor Park hotel, Washington Hebrew Congregation, Tom Lawson, Cowboy Ray Allen, Harod the Great, St. Clements Church, and a cathedral.
  - Artwork, 1959-1975 (Box 39)
    Artwork from the Smithsonian and Woodlawn. (negatives)
  - Artwork, 1960s (Box 40)
    Artwork in the form of posters, including the making of the posters.
  - Artwork, 1960s (Box 48)
    More posters as artwork as well as photographs of various paintings and other forms of art.
  - Artwork, 1960s (Box 51)
    Artwork from inside the White House, the Iranian Embassy and at various Washington, D.C., monuments.
  - Artwork, 1947, 1952 (Box 53)
    Artwork in this box includes art inside the Gadsby Tavern and images of Christmas stockings and Christmas card images. (negatives)
  - Artwork, undated (Box 59)
    Images of artwork in the White House, Waynewood, and Embassies.
  - Miscellaneous, 1950s (Box 69, Folder 7)
    Images of art in larger print formats.
- Series 4: Publications, 1942-1994
  This series contains publications for which Charles Baptie provided pictures or helped print at his studio. The series includes many brochures and pamphlets, guide books, logos, small print books, magazines, and poetry collections.
  - Baseball Book, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
    A book about baseball.
  - Encyclopedia of American History, undated (Box 3, Folder 4-21)
    Encyclopedia of American History
  - History of the Civil War, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    History of the Civil War
  - Northern Virginia Guide Books Pictures, 1960s (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Northern Virginia Guide Book.
  - Advertising, 1950s (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Publications for advertisements
  - George Hamill, 1950s (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Publications for the George Hamill [For Mayor] campaign.
  - Besley, Oliver, 1950s (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Publication items entitled Besley, Oliver.
  - Brochures, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Brochures for George Mason College.
  - Printed materials, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Printed materials for George Mason College.
  - Texaco- Prints and Negatives, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 35)
    Publication materials for Texaco.
  - Christmas card photos, Religious program bulletin, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Publication items for Christmas cards and a religious program bulletin
  - Data for Speedlight, 1940s-1950s (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Publication items for Speedlight
  - Publications, 1959-1965 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Camera on Assignment flyer; American Forests magazine (May 1959); and In Washington: The National Society Daughters of the American Revolution (1965).
  - Northern Virginia: Fifty Fabulous Years, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    New Comer's/ Spring issue 1990 of Northern Virginian since 1971.
  - Guide Book photos, 1960s (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Guide book of Northern Virginia photographs.
  - Scientific publication photos, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Scientific photographs for publications.
  - Army equipment, 1960s (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Posed military uniform scene.
  - Logos, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Logos and cover pages for publications.
  - Newspaper, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    Newspaper about Pearl Harbor with photographs.
  - Lunes, 1973 (Box 18)
    Poems by Margaret Gibson; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - The Ghetto, 1976 (Box 18)
    Living Poetry by Ann Sawyer Berkley; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - Dorothy Heizer, 1972 (Box 18)
    Dorothy Heizer: the Artist and her Dolls by Helen Bullard; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - Iceland's 20th Century Composers, 1977 (Box 18)
    Iceland's 20th Century Composers and a Listening of their works by Amanda Burt, Ph.D.; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - The Historical Society of Fairfax County, VA, 1980 (Box 18)
    Volume 16; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - Maplewood, 1970 (Box 18)
    Maplewood by Diane N. Rafuse; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - The Historical Society of Fairfax Country, VA, 1978-1979 (Box 18)
    Volume 15; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - Song Peddler, 1979 (Box 18)
    By Ramona Graham Cook; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - Notes and Stuff, 1972 (Box 18)
    Notes n Stuff: Simply Fundamentals of Music by Amanda M. Burt, Ph.D.;printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - Doing Things and Happenings, 1979 (Box 18)
    Doing Things and Happenings: A Book of Poems for Boys and Girls by Mary Goodlet Kellogg; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - Fairfax Law Library, 1983 (Box 18)
    A guide to resources and services; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - Fort Burd, 1981 (Box 18)
    Fort Burd: Redstones Historic Frontier Fort: A Historical Account by Richard A. Sells; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - The Thorn and the Rose, 1974 (Box 18)
    Written by Zenia L. Koladis; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - 3rd Latin American Audio Visual Communications Seminar, 1958 (Box 18)
    Article written by Baptie, "Still Photography Techniques for Use in Audiovisual Aids"
  - Centreville Virginia: It's History and Architecture, 1978 (Box 18)
    Written by Eugenia B. Smith; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - Walrus, 1979 (Box 18)
    Written by Michele Moure Elliott; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - Catalog of The Photographic Archive of Fairfax County, VA, 1981 (Box 18)
    Assembled by the Fairfax County Historical Commission; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - Here's the Dirt, 1984 (Box 18)
    By George Boggs Roscoe; printed by Charles Baptie Studios.
  - Gunston Hall Pamphlet, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Pamphlet for Gunston Hall.
  - Woodlawn Pamphlet, 1950s (Box 19, Folder 4)
    Pamphlet for Woodlawn Plantation.
  - Symposium, 1967 (Box 20)
    Spring 1967 Symposium.
  - Erudite, 1967 (Box 20)
    Erudite book.
  - Fallout, 1967 (Box 20)
    Fallout book.
  - Page, 1967 (Box 20)
    Page book by the W.T. Woodson High School.
  - the Walrus, 1978 (Box 20)
    The Walrus, a book printed by Baptie Studios
  - Hazelton Laboratories, Inc, 1965 (Box 20)
    1965 Annual Report for Hazelton Labs
  - National Limestone Institute, 1976 (Box 20)
    1976 issue of the National Limestone Institute publication.
  - National Limestone Institute, 1983 (Box 20)
    1983 issue of the National Limestone Institute publication.
  - St. Agnes Alumnae Magazine, 1972 (Box 20)
    1972 St. Agnes Alumnae magazine.
  - La Voz de Colombia en Washington, 1982 (Box 20)
    July-August 1982 issue of La Voz de Colombia en Washington.
  - Painting Hex Signs, 1973 (Box 20)
    Painting Hex signs by Kay Gephart.
  - Popular Marches sheet music, 1961 (Box 20)
    Sheet music for Battle of Manassas for piano.
  - Camera...On Assignment, 1957 (Box 20)
    Camera on Assignment by Ollie Atkins and Charles Baptie.
  - papers for Brazil publication, 1958 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    Papers dealing with a publication about Brazil.
  - Publications, 1950s (Box 47)
    Images to be used for Smithsonian Guidebook publication.
  - Publications, 1960s (Box 53)
    Charles Fenwick library publication image.
  - , 1952-1953 (Box 60, Folder 1-7)
    Publication images entitled, The Starling Nuisance: He's Driving Everybody Crazy; He makes the Brass see Red; The man Ike trusts with the cash; He runs the show for Ike; Silliest statues you ever saw; How to clean a dirty city; and I watched Eisenhower Campaign.
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1956-1984 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Newspaper clippings.
  - Camera Scraps, undated (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Camera scraps publication pages.
  - Publications, 1970s (Box 65)
    Gunston Hall publication proofs.
  - Washington Portrait, 1953 (Box 67)
    Copy of Washington Portrait, a book Charles Baptie helped illustrate with photographs.
  - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    Miscellaneous papers dealing with publications.
  - Dog book, 1946 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    Photos and text for Herkie the Pup.
  - Brazil Publication, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Publication materials for a book about Brazil.
  - Brazil Publication, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Small Press Publications, 1966-1994 (Box 70)
    Small publications from Washington, D.C. and Northern Virginia. Content includes: Color Picture Book of Washington; The Rag and Bone Shop, a book of poetry by C.J.S. Durham, 1985; Records of Dettingen Parish, 1745-1802; The Blueprint, student handbook for W.T. Woodson High School, 1966; Student Handbook, for Annandale High School, 1965; Dorothy Heizer The Artist and Her Dolls, by Helen Bullard, 1972; Measure and Beat: Recipes From the musicians and friends of the Fairfax Symphony Orchestra; Crafts and Craftsmen of the Tennessee Mountains, by Helen Bullard, 1976; Moorefield, a guide to the historical home of Jeremiah Moore by Thomas V. DiBacco, 1971; Green Spring Farm, a guide to the historic home by Ross and Nan Netherton, two editions 1970 and 1975; Willian Ray Brown A Tribute; Dawn Song, a book of poetry by Margaret Christensen Gilbert, 1977; Lee Mansion, a guide to the historic home of Robert E. Lee by Randle Bond Truett, 1943; J. G. Whittier Middle School Year Book, 1980-1981; Colvin Run Mill, a guide to the historic mill by Ross D. Netherton, 1976; The Conservative Virginian Magazine, 1980; The Official Manual and Selective Music List for the Virginia Band and Orchestra Directors' Association, 1972-1975. Also a folder of small pamphlets and programs including: Friends of the Fairfax County Jail; Reston Summer Festival, 1972; Annandale High School Graduation Excersizes program, 1976; The Fairfax Resolves, reproduction of George Mason's document, 1974; Carlyle House Historic Park guide pamphlet; System Sciences Corporation holiday greeting card; Northern Virginia Region High School Football Championships program, 1994.
  - Capital Airlines, 1940s-1950s (Box 70)
    Newspaper clippings and postcards relating to Capital Airlines. Capitaliner magazine and airline napkin.
- Series 5: Texaco Stations, 1950-1972
  This series contains negatives of Texaco stations in the greater Washington, D.C., area. There are aerial views and on-the-ground images, as well as plans, blueprints, portraits, and vehicles included in the collection.
  - Texaco, 1951-1969 (Box 4, Folder 1-43)
    Images include company's logo; a mural; rust proofing trucks; salesmen; N.D, no location; 1950-1960s; 1964; 1965; 1966; 1967; 1968; 1969; 4th and Florida N.E.; 11th Street S.E.; Alexandria; Annandale; Annandale Road and Arlington Boulevard, Aerial View of Jefferson Village; Aerial views of Columbia Pike-Barcroft Area; Aerial view of southeast edge of Beacon Field; Beltway near Andrews Field Authority Road; Bender - US 1; Berryville; Aerial vies of Bethesda, MD area; Blau Road and Cedar; Brown Texaco 1964; South Capitol and Livingston Road; Capitol Plaza; Chantilly; Aerial views of Cherrydale and Lee Highway; Aerial views of Clearwood Road and Rhode Island Avenue; miscellaneous; Darnstown; Democracy Boulevard; Dodge Park; East Capitol and 13th N.E.; People Fairfax; Fairfax Circle; Fairfax Drive and 25th Street, Falls Church; Forestville; Fort Hunt and Route 1; Franconia; and Franconia Road.
  - Texaco, 1952-1968 (Box 5, Folder 1-56)
    These folders contain images of Bob H; Hillcrest Drive, off Branch Avenue, NE; Hillcrest Gardens; I-66 and Route 234; Interchange I-95; I-495 and River Road; Indian Head Highway; Bud Johnson; Kamp Washington near Fairfax; Route 66 and Route 50, Kamp Washington; Langley; Lanham; Laurel; Leesburg Pike and S. Walter Reed Drive; SE 1/2 M Street; Manassas; Route 66, Manassas; Massachusetts Avenue at District Lane; McCoy Texaco; Bill Me; Morningside Area; Mt. Vernon Boulevard and 10th Street; New York Avenue and Bladensburg Road; New York Avenue at 5th Street; Nicholas and South Capitol; aerial view northeast section of Washington, D.C.,; Oakton; Olney, MD; Piney Branch and Carroll; Potomac, MD; Riggs Road Intersection; aerial view River Road; Rocking Horse and Bioling Brook; Rockville; US 240 - Rockville; aerial view of Route 1 near Plant and Industrial Boulevard; Route 50 at 56th Street; Route 240 between Rockville and Naval Hospital; Route 495, Defense Highway; Seminary Road and Shirley Highway; Route 277-Route 9 Stephen City; Telegraph Road; Tyson's Corner; University of Maryland; Gerry Utter Texaco; Wheaton, MD; Route 11, Winchester, VA; Route 50 and Route 81, Winchester, VA; and Winchester, VA.
  - Texaco, 1952-1972 (Box 12, Folder 1-43)